<?xml version="1.0"?>

<log>

	<logentry

	   revision="34576">

		<author>arv@chromium.org</author>

		<date>2009-12-15T18:47:14.827970Z</date>

		<msg>
			NTP: Hide the notifier when restoring all removed thumbnails.



			BUG=29952

			TEST=Blacklist a thumbanil. This shows the notifier. Then restore all remove

			thumbnails. The notifier should be hidden now.



			Review URL: http://codereview.chromium.org/494013
		</msg>

	</logentry>

	<logentry

	   revision="34577">

		<author>dkegel@google.com</author>

		<date>2009-12-15T19:06:34.652156Z</date>

		<msg>
			Absolutify suppression directories so they survive the cd.



			Use the 'right' version of valgrind.  Later, once we have

			our patches in, we need to implement

			the searching code from ../valgrind/valgrind.sh.



			BUG=none

			TEST=wine bot actually runs valgrind on unit_tests

			Review URL: http://codereview.chromium.org/507011
		</msg>

	</logentry>

	<logentry

	   revision="34578">

		<author>akalin@chromium.org</author>

		<date>2009-12-15T19:20:08.730893Z</date>

		<msg>
			Implemented OS X version of NetworkStatusDetectorTaskMac.



			BUG=none

			TEST=trybots,manual testing



			Review URL: http://codereview.chromium.org/485004
		</msg>

	</logentry>

	<logentry

	   revision="34579">

		<author>ojan@chromium.org</author>

		<date>2009-12-15T19:23:30.057310Z</date>

		<msg>
			Add one more test that got flaky after sharding the http tests.

			And mark the flaky tests from moving to apache and sharding

			the http tests as part of the umbrella 9798 bug.

			Review URL: http://codereview.chromium.org/501023
		</msg>

	</logentry>

	<logentry

	   revision="34580">

		<author>andybons@chromium.org</author>

		<date>2009-12-15T19:25:51.528589Z</date>

		<msg>
			Reattempt at r465143. The UI tests rely too heavily on the current behavior of closing the last window indicating exiting the entire app, so that is left alone for now with a TODO added.

			From the old description:

			Mac: Fixes bug where extension background hosts were being cleared when the last window was closed. It assumed that this meant the app was closing. Not the case with Mac apps. Added a mac-only notification APP_TERMINATED and use that to perform cleanup upon shutdown.



			TEST=More description in the bug, but basically just make sure that background views stick around even after you've closed the last window.

			BUG=28666

			Review URL: http://codereview.chromium.org/502012
		</msg>

	</logentry>

</log>

